const practice_trials = {
    sliderRating: [
        {
	    QUD: "Test",
	    picture: "<a>Test, Test, Test</a",
            question: "How do you feel today?",
            optionLeft: "awful",
            optionRight: "great"
        },
    ],
}

const main_trials_transcript = {

   sliderRating: [
        {
	    QUD: "Transcript",
	    picture: '<a>We`re losing the Greek diners in New York. We`re losing the places that you can go to get a cup of coffee, read the newspaper, have a sandwich. <br /> <br />You have all these places now with tiny tables. It`s Artisinal, grass-fed, all this crab.</a',           
	    question: "How tiny are the tables the speaker is referring to?",
            optionLeft: "children`s table",
            optionRight: "knight`s table"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>It is going to move towards Mexico, spread the cloud cover our way. There`s small tiny chance of a shower or two as that low continues to one closer to Baja.</a",
	    question: "What is the chance of a shower according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "0%",
            optionRight: "100%"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>And NASA hopes it improves our accuracy and our ability to forecast their intensity in the future. The satellites, 8 tiny ones, will be spread across the world`s oceans coming up in the next few months.</a",
	    question: "What size are the satellites according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as small as a CD",
            optionRight: "as big as the Death Star"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>As we stand there melting, this chick comes gunning up the side of the line, tall, beautiful girl.</a",
	    question: "How tall is the girl gunning up the side of the line according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as tall as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as a basketball player in the NBL"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>I tell you what: Craig Sager was a tall guy.<br />I was like wow, you are tall!</a",
	    question: "How tall is Craig Sager according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as tall as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as a basketball player in the NBL"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>I was so nervous because I thought he was so attractive and I didnt know quite how to deal with that as, you know, I`m supposed to be the director.</a",
	    question: "How attractive is the man referred to by the speaker according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "exceptionally repulsive",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Narrator: Her name was Lucy and for some time, as she couldn`t help but notice, a particular customer turned up at almost all the teller windows except hers.<br /> <br />Lucy: He was a very, very attractive man.</a",
	    question: "How attractive was the customer according to the Lucy?",
            optionLeft: "the least attractive person in the world",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Narrator: lucky in love with her.<br /> <br />Woman: I found him very attractive and interesting, and he was fun to talk to.</a",
	    question: "How happy is the dog according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "exceptionally repulsive",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Woman 1: So what do you think?<br /> <br />Man: What size is it?<br /> <br />Woman 2: I love the size of the palm trees.<br /> <br />Man: I really only have one problem with this suit: it`s very ugly, okay?<br /> <br />Woman 2: It`s not.<br /> <br />Man: I`d actually wear it but its very ugly.<br /> <br />Woman 2: It`s beautiful</a",
	    question: "How ugly is the suit according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most ugliest suit he has ever seen",
            optionRight: "not ugly at all, but very beautiful"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Narrator: …in this room as the delegates turned their anger at Cruz`s wife Heidi, who had to be escorted out.<br /> <br />Cruz: Well, people behind her were getting very ugly and physically approaching her, and it was not a pretty situation.</a",
	    question: "How were the people behaving around his wife according to the Cruz?",
            optionLeft: "very polite",
            optionRight: "in the most horrible way"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Interviewer: Six minute.<br /> <br />Musician:A six-minute song, yeah. Everyone kept trying…<br /> <br />Interviewer: You did got carried away, did you?<br /> <br />Musician: Yeah, everyone kept trying to make that my single and I said I don`t know if America has six minutes of attention span, you know. Only have 140 characters most of the time, to get your point across.<br /> <br />But I… I`m happy that I went ahead and kept it, and a third man was very adamant with me about having it be the kickoff to the album.</a",
	    question: "How does the musician feel about keeping the six-minute song?",
            optionLeft: "it is the thing she regrets most in life",
            optionRight: "the happiest she has ever felt about anything"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Host: Hi Mary, how are you?<br /> <br />Mary: I`m great, how are you?<br /><br />Host: I`m good. We`re so happy that you`re here.<br /> <br />Mary: I`m so happy to be here.<br /> <br />Host: We`re all such fans of you down here.<br /> <br />Mary: Thank you!</a",
	    question: "How happy is the host about having Mary on the show?",
            optionLeft: "very unhappy",
            optionRight: "happiest day of life"
        },
	
	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Kathy, Michael, we just talked with that little girl kidnapped earlier this afternoon: She is happy, she`s in good spirits and all smiles when we saw her just about 20 minutes ago.<br /> <br />The frightening ordeal happened in the parking lot, right here</a",
	    question: "How happy is the little girl according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very unhappy",
            optionRight: "happiest girl in the world"
        },
	
	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>She was a big part of my childhood as Princess Leia, you know. So I mean, she was just a great icon and she will definitely be missed for sure.<br /> <br/>So that`s very sad, very heart breaking.</a",
	    question: "How does the speaker feel about the situation?",
            optionLeft: "she is unconsolably sad about it",
            optionRight: "she is happy about it"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Reporter: The Brazilian army is going to send a military plane here to take the bodies back around this time tomorrow for what will be of course an incredibly sad repatriation mission.<br /> <br />News anchor: Thank you so much. Such a tragedy, that awful crash.</a",
	    question: "How sad is the repatriation mission according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "enormously sad",
            optionRight: "it`s a very happy mission"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>So, ehm, I mean, it`s so sad. We talked to so many family members of these victims. Often Times the victims themselves don`t realize it`s a scam. They think they really have won a huge prize or that they are corresponding with a psychic who is going to help them turn their lives around.</a",
	    question: "How sad is the situation according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "enormously sad",
            optionRight: "it`s a very happy situation"
       },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Man 1: Kerry has made what I think is the most important speech of an American policy maker in decades but politically it clearly is now dead in the water.<br /> <br />Woman: So on that note, Aaron, why wasn`t this speech given sooner?<br /> <br />Aaron: Ah-ha, and thats a very interesting question.</a",
	    question: "How interesting is the question according to Aaron?",
            optionLeft: "completely irrelevant",
            optionRight: "most interesting question in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Now it`s taking shape with letters from Vladimir Putin to Donald Trump with their exchange on potential nuclear armament and what not.<br /> <br />So, I think this is going to be a very interesting world to unfold in the next four years.</a",
	    question: "How interesting is the situation going to become according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "as interesting as never before"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>And whatever this administration is going to cook up, is going to pose all sorts of fascinating challenges we were not expecting and working on that stuff is going to be unifying because he`s planning to govern, from who he's appointing, he seems to be planning on governing from a really, really out there place, and I think that`s going to make for a very interesting time sort of in the opposition, kind of in the resistance.</a",
	    question: "How interesting will the situation become for the opposition according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "as interesting as never before"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Host: He`s now living in the `50s and kind of -- just kind of resenting everyone around him, his wife, his kids.<br />And you get to see -- Oh it`s just very interesting, you know the characters that it -- every character`s got something.<br /> <br />Guest: Yeah they do.<br /> <br />Host: I love everyone in it. And you just knock it out of the park again.<br /> <br />Guest: Thank you.<br /> <br />Host: And I go: ``Oh, my Gosh, you look beautiful´´.</a",
	    question: "How interesting is the movie or show the Host talks about according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "the most interesting movie/show in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>There`s a group called the Institute for the Study of war, which puts a very interesting maps once meant to show where the bombardment is.<br />And so they show the Russian bombardment.<br />And you can see these little explosives around Aleppo</a",
	    question: "How interesting are the maps of bombardment according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "the most interesting things in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Gayle: Have you ever driven a car at night and turned off headlights just just for grins, just to see what would happen?<br /> <br />Woman 2: No, Gayle, I haven`t.<br /> <br />Gayle: I did that when I was younger, just to see, then you quickly turn them back on. It was young and foolish, I get it.<br /> <br />Woman 2: But I like the new cars, where the headlights do the high beam probing by itself.<br /> <br />Gayle: I like them too. That was very important information.<br /> <br />Man: Do you still have that sense of adventure?<br /> <br />Gayle: No, I have gotten very boring in my old age.</a",
	    question: "How boring has Gayle become according to herself?",
            optionLeft: "as boring as one could become",
            optionRight: "she is the most interesting person in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Host: Oh look, she seems sweet with Remi.<br /> <br />Guest: She is, well, because I`m not holding him. Like anytime I hold him, it`s like: I don`t know what you are doing in my spot. She doesn`t like that.<br /> <br />Host: She`s jealous of him?<br /> <br />Guest: She is so jealous in that moment, but she loves him. She loves feeding him and she loves -- I`m such a mom, I`m so boring, I`m sorry, keep talking about my kids. Host: I`m asking, it`s okay.</a",
	     question: "How boring has the Guest become according to herself?",
            optionLeft: "as boring as one could become",
            optionRight: "she is the most interesting person in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>The cameras don`t even cover her protesters, that`s just bad.<br />See, I like it when the camera covers the protesters, because then they finally show how many people you have at these things.<br />Her protesters have so little enthusiasm for her and they are so boring that the cameras don`t follow them, so sad when you think about it.</a",
	     question: "How boring are `her`protesters according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most boring people in the world",
            optionRight: "the most interesting and active people in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
           picture: "<a>Woman 1: I went on a date a year ago and had to leave the guy. It was terrible but he was so boring and he was kind and sweet but he was just…<br /> <br />Women 2: What did he do?</a",
	    question: "How boring was her date according to Woman 1?",
           optionLeft: "the most boring person in the world",
           optionRight: "the most interesting person in the world"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>I like to do the morning shift and he picks Eva up from school. So I take Eva to school in the morning usually and then come back and have my coffee and just relax and then if I -- I don`t know. It`s so -- maybe go grocery shopping. It`s so boring.</a",
	    question: "How boring is her morning according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "there is nothing more boring than her mornings",
            optionRight: "her mornings are the most interesting mornings one can have"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>And I think Clinton has an advantage over Sanders speaking in sometimes complicated, sometimes incredibly boring detail about what she would do as president.</a",
	    question: "How boring are the details in which Clinton explains her plans according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most tiring possible",
            optionRight: "very interesting"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Bill Hall Jr. was a self-made man with plenty of money in the bank, a loving wife, and a loving family. But he also had a very big secret, one that would tear that loving family apart.</a",
	    question: "How big is Bill Hall Jr.`s secret according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very unimportant trifle",
            optionRight: "the secret will forever change the lives of many in a negative way if it blows up"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>And aside from those fallen trees and downed power lines we are also seeing some very big waves.</a",
	    question: "How hbig are the waves according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "barely noticeable",
            optionRight: "tidal waves"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>And that is just the Centers for Disease Control and prevention which is a very big big operation inside a giant operation called the Department of Health and Human Services which is inside that giant thing called the government of the United States of America.</a",
	    question: "How big are the Centers of Disease Control and prevention according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as big as a local pharmacy",
            optionRight: "has big as Walmart (largest company in the world)"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>You have my money, what are you going to do with that money? You`re going to recycle that money, probably back into the U.S. economy.<br />So, capital inflows are a very big part of trade. And I don`t think the Trump campaign has really understood that.</a",
	    question: "How important is capital inflow to trade according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "negligible and only a small part, if any",
            optionRight: "most important and biggest part"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>8:28 is the time, we've got three things going own right now one very big backup here so this has been going on for the last two hours, not a Sig Alert* they assure us, should be out of the way shortly.<br /><br />*defined by the California Highway Patrol (CHP) as ``any unplanned event that causes the closing of one lane of traffic for 30 minutes or more´ (https://web.archive.org/web/20150415222304/http://www.sigalert.com/Faq.asp?lat=37.87913&lon=-122.07842&z=2).</a",
	    question: "How big is the backup according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "tiny, it is hardly a backup at all",
            optionRight: "the largest backup the world has ever seen"
        },
	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>What are they swearing allegiance to? They are not swearing allegiance to France but to an extreme fraction of Islam, that represents, by the way, a very small portion of the entire religion.</a",
	    question: "How large is the extreme fraction of Islam in the religion according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "negligible, almost none",
            optionRight: "almost all people of Islam belong to the extreme fraction"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>I grew up listening to those records, you know. It`s funny, my Mom`s like a very small white woman, and my dad always describes that club as, like, the place -- like black people in the bay know, like, Wednesday nights, you go see this little white lady spin at the Graduate.</a",
	    question: "How small is his mother according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as small as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as an NBA player"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Woman: What is one thing people would be surprised to know about me?<br /><br />Man: Your late night eating habits. It`s generally a very small sweet and a large cup of milk.</a",
	    question: "How small is the sweet according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "tiny, as small as a grain of rice",
            optionRight: "very large, about the size of a wedding cake"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>Host: But it must be a nightmare to shoot there.<br /><br />Guest: Yes, it is like a beautiful nightmare.<br /><br />Host: Okay.<br /><br />Guest: Yeah, like so you travel everywhere by very small boat, which is cool. And then every morning you rise to the sound of like an opera singer</a",
	    question: "How small is the boat according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small, one person can barely sit in it",
            optionRight: "the size of a cruise ship"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>What has happened already in Aleppo is unconscionable. But there remains tens of thousands of lives that are now concentrated into a very small area of Aleppo.</a",
	    question: "How small is the area according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small that nobody can move",
            optionRight: "open area, where everyone has their own property and land"
        },

	{
	    QUD: "Transcript",            
            picture: "<a>I was driving out of this very sharp turn. We were driving in Italy, in Florence and doing this driving scene. And the streets are so small and for some reason , I was in this huge car. My character kind of had an enormous kind of four-wheel drive thing. </a",
	    question: "How wide are the streets in Florence according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small, a car barely fit",
            optionRight: "so side, 3 Trucks can easily fit"
        }
    ],
}

const main_trials_audio = {

    sliderRating_Audio: [
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=1c5325da-ce7f-11e6-8ca3-089e01ba034d&start=2727.8&end=2742.2' type=audio/wav>/audio",
 	    question: "How tiny are the tables the speaker is referring to?",
            optionLeft: "children`s table",
            optionRight: "knight`s table"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=9a447f36-c6bc-11e6-b97f-089e01ba0338&start=1082.42&end=1092.8' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "What is the chance of a shower according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "0%",
            optionRight: "100%"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=232a6b90-c5db-11e6-a9b1-e7ec6cb6e467&start=2233.86&end=2247.64' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "What size are the satellites according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as small as a CD",
            optionRight: "as big as the Death Star"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=1e64354c-87aa-11e6-87b4-089e01ba0770&start=2931.59&end=2937.96' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How tall is the girl gunning up the side of the line according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as tall as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as a basketball player in the NBL"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=8e56ec48-c38f-11e6-bdfb-2c600c9500f4&start=1033.33&end=1037.57' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How tall is Craig Sager according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as tall as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as a basketball player in the NBL"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=6a3091c4-717e-11e6-91df-089e01ba0326&start=1348.7&end=1356.48' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How attractive is the man referred to by the speaker according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "exceptionally repulsive",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=eb2d9a0c-ce1c-11e5-ad2f-089e01ba0326&start=182.34&end=195.03' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How attractive was the customer according to the Lucy?",
            optionLeft: "the least attractive person in the world",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=c05cacce-b75f-11e5-ade7-089e01ba0326&start=298.13&end=309.58' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How happy is the dog according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "exceptionally repulsive",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=70d11e34-5ea2-11e6-b949-089e01ba034d&start=1377&end=1390.58' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How ugly is the suit according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most ugliest suit he has ever seen",
            optionRight: "not ugly at all, but very beautiful"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=51634a8c-4f1a-11e6-868f-089e01ba0770&start=226.3&end=239.89' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How were the people behaving around his wife according to the Cruz?",
            optionLeft: "very polite",
            optionRight: "in the most horrible way"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=6985b450-cf09-11e6-9606-089e01ba0326&start=971.75&end=1001.31' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How does the musician feel about keeping the six-minute song?",
            optionLeft: "it is the thing she regrets most in life",
            optionRight: "the happiest she has ever felt about anything"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=22c81d1c-ce6b-11e6-8fd0-089e01ba0335&start=411.38&end=421.05' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How happy is the host about having Mary on the show?",
            optionLeft: "very unhappy",
            optionRight: "happiest day of life"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=4b0831e4-ce2b-11e6-ad46-089e01ba0326&start=72.1&end=84.5' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How happy is the little girl according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very unhappy",
            optionRight: "happiest girl in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=4f475e06-cd0e-11e6-b11e-089e01ba0338&start=2036.98&end=2049.57' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How does the speaker feel about the situation?",
            optionLeft: "she is unconsolably sad about it",
            optionRight: "she is happy about it"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=5519f172-b698-11e6-a31c-089e01ba0326&start=394.41&end=411.0' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How sad is the repatriation mission according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "enormously sad",
            optionRight: "it`s a very happy mission"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=80bb68d6-80ee-11e6-99c9-2c600c9500f4&start=1825.16&end=1842.22' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How sad is the situation according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "enormously sad",
            optionRight: "it`s a very happy situation"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=d5f7c65e-cd2f-11e6-b020-2c600c9500f4&start=1261.74&end=1279.12' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How interesting is the question according to Aaron?",
            optionLeft: "completely irrelevant",
            optionRight: "most interesting question in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=0717d42c-c9f2-11e6-ac1a-089e01ba0326&start=2364.58&end=2380.57' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How interesting is the situation going to become according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "as interesting as never before"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=cf80f0f6-c821-11e6-86ab-089e01ba0326&start=1763.51&end=1783.89' type=audio/wav>/audio",
	    question: "How interesting will the situation become for the opposition according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "as interesting as never before"
    },
        {   
        QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=25a5156a-c819-11e6-9174-089e01ba0326&start=1619.36&end=1637.56' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How interesting is the movie or show the Host talks about according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "the most interesting movie/show in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=fd538d1e-c20d-11e6-809b-089e01ba034d&start=2155.96&end=2167.5' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How interesting are the maps of bombardment according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "the most interesting things in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=52596f7e-9abb-11e6-b85a-089e01ba0770&start=2829.12&end=2852.59' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How boring has Gayle become according to herself?",
            optionLeft: "as boring as one could become",
            optionRight: "she is the most interesting person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=8375bfb2-8a86-11e6-b3a1-089e01ba034d&start=1462.09&end=1485.32' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How boring has the Guest become according to herself?",
            optionLeft: "as boring as one could become",
            optionRight: "she is the most interesting person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=0a4db1e0-6a2d-11e6-a28a-089e01ba034d&start=3110.58&end=3128.91' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How boring are `her` protesters according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most boring people in the world",
            optionRight: "the most interesting and active people in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=55b8be18-54ed-11e6-855f-089e01ba0335&start=2461.93&end=2473.89' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How boring was her date according to Woman 1?",
            optionLeft: "the most boring person in the world",
            optionRight: "the most interesting person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=cac3c3ea-1d22-11e6-b216-089e01ba0326&start=4530.85&end=4544.62' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How boring is her morning according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "there is nothing more boring than her mornings",
            optionRight: "her mornings are the most interesting mornings one can have"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=fa3f37f8-c4cb-11e5-800a-089e01ba0335&start=564.49&end=575.38' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How boring are the details in which Clinton explains her plans according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most tiring possible",
            optionRight: "very interesting"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=b5fd5666-ab65-11e6-bc38-089e01ba0770&start=110.82&end=120.88' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How big is Bill Hall Jr.`s secret according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very unimportant trifle",
            optionRight: "the secret will forever change the lives of many in a negative way if it blows up"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=ba7f4198-b91d-11e6-aacf-2c600c9500f4&start=407.53&end=415.3' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How big are the waves according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "barely noticeable",
            optionRight: "tidal waves"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=c486da34-aba8-11e6-8597-089e01ba0326&start=508.83&end=527.85' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How big are the Centers of Disease Control and prevention according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as big as a local pharmacy",
            optionRight: "has big as Walmart (largest company in the world)"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=f2d807ce-a18e-11e6-8988-089e01ba0770&start=584.16&end=599.96' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How important is capital inflow to trade according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "negligible and only a small part, if any",
            optionRight: "most important and biggest part"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=4eca3502-cd0e-11e6-bac3-089e01ba0335&start=5282.92&end=5295.33' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How big is the backup according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "tiny, it is hardly a backup at all",
            optionRight: "the largest backup the world has ever seen"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=f5a320f8-ad21-11e6-b422-089e01ba0326&start=3228.57&end=3237.19' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How large is the extreme fraction of Islam in the religion according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "negligible, almost none",
            optionRight: "almost all people of Islam belong to the extreme fraction"
    },
        {
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=dc086c5a-a585-11e6-a674-089e01ba0326&start=2651.72&end=2669.58' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How small is his mother according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as small as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as an NBA player"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=16dbe2e4-a4be-11e6-9a66-089e01ba0335&start=1273.87&end=1285.03' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How small is the sweet according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "tiny, as small as a grain of rice",
            optionRight: "very large, about the size of a wedding cake"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=22d6cbb4-ce6b-11e6-af30-089e01ba0326&start=2423.11&end=2438.26' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How small is the boat according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small, one person can barely sit in it",
            optionRight: "the size of a cruise ship"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=ae6f90b2-c2f8-11e6-a1c7-089e01ba0338&start=2360.2&end=2372.97' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How small is the area according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small that nobody can move",
            optionRight: "open area, where everyone has their own property and land"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Audio", 
 	    stimulus:"<audio controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_wav_snippet.cgi?file=56d54f8e-b57b-11e6-ad52-089e01ba0770&start=5779.63&end=5793.0' type=audio/wav>/audio",
            question: "How wide are the streets in Florence according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small, a car barely fit",
            optionRight: "so side, 3 Trucks can easily fit"
         }
     ],
}

const main_trials_video = {
    sliderRating_Video: [
        {
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=1c5325da-ce7f-11e6-8ca3-089e01ba034d&start=2727.8&end=2742.2' type='video/mp4'>/video", 
            question: "How tiny are the tables the speaker is referring to?",
            optionLeft: "children`s table",
            optionRight: "knight`s table"
        },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=9a447f36-c6bc-11e6-b97f-089e01ba0338&start=1082.42&end=1092.8' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "What is the chance of a shower according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "0%",
            optionRight: "100%"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=232a6b90-c5db-11e6-a9b1-e7ec6cb6e467&start=2233.86&end=2247.64' type='video/mp4'>/video",
	    question: "What size are the satellites according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as small as a CD",
            optionRight: "as big as the Death Star"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=1e64354c-87aa-11e6-87b4-089e01ba0770&start=2931.59&end=2937.96' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How tall is the girl gunning up the side of the line according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as tall as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as a basketball player in the NBL"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=8e56ec48-c38f-11e6-bdfb-2c600c9500f4&start=1033.33&end=1037.57' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How tall is Craig Sager according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as tall as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as a basketball player in the NBL"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=6a3091c4-717e-11e6-91df-089e01ba0326&start=1348.7&end=1356.48' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How attractive is the man referred to by the speaker according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "exceptionally repulsive",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=eb2d9a0c-ce1c-11e5-ad2f-089e01ba0326&start=182.34&end=195.03' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How attractive was the customer according to the Lucy?",
            optionLeft: "the least attractive person in the world",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=c05cacce-b75f-11e5-ade7-089e01ba0326&start=298.13&end=309.74' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How happy is the dog according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "exceptionally repulsive",
            optionRight: "the most attractive person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=70d11e34-5ea2-11e6-b949-089e01ba034d&start=1377&end=1390.58' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How ugly is the suit according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most ugliest suit he has ever seen",
            optionRight: "not ugly at all, but very beautiful"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=51634a8c-4f1a-11e6-868f-089e01ba0770&start=226.3&end=239.89' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How were the people behaving around his wife according to the Cruz?",
            optionLeft: "very polite",
            optionRight: "in the most horrible way"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=6985b450-cf09-11e6-9606-089e01ba0326&start=971.75&end=1001.31' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How does the musician feel about keeping the six-minute song?",
            optionLeft: "it is the thing she regrets most in life",
            optionRight: "the happiest she has ever felt about anything"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=22c81d1c-ce6b-11e6-8fd0-089e01ba0335&start=411.38&end=421.05' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How happy is the host about having Mary on the show?",
            optionLeft: "very unhappy",
            optionRight: "happiest day of life"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=4b0831e4-ce2b-11e6-ad46-089e01ba0326&start=72.1&end=84.5' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How happy is the little girl according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very unhappy",
            optionRight: "happiest girl in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=4f475e06-cd0e-11e6-b11e-089e01ba0338&start=2036.98&end=2049.57' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How does the speaker feel about the situation?",
            optionLeft: "she is unconsolably sad about it",
            optionRight: "she is happy about it"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=5519f172-b698-11e6-a31c-089e01ba0326&start=394.41&end=411.0' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How sad is the repatriation mission according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "enormously sad",
            optionRight: "it`s a very happy mission"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=80bb68d6-80ee-11e6-99c9-2c600c9500f4&start=1825.16&end=1842.22' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How sad is the situation according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "enormously sad",
            optionRight: "it`s a very happy situation"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=d5f7c65e-cd2f-11e6-b020-2c600c9500f4&start=1261.74&end=1279.12' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How interesting is the question according to Aaron?",
            optionLeft: "completely irrelevant",
            optionRight: "most interesting question in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=0717d42c-c9f2-11e6-ac1a-089e01ba0326&start=2364.58&end=2380.57' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How interesting is the situation going to become according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "as interesting as never before"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=cf80f0f6-c821-11e6-86ab-089e01ba0326&start=1763.51&end=1783.89' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How interesting will the situation become for the opposition according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "as interesting as never before"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=25a5156a-c819-11e6-9174-089e01ba0326&start=1619.36&end=1637.56' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How interesting is the movie or show the Host talks about according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "the most interesting movie/show in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=fd538d1e-c20d-11e6-809b-089e01ba034d&start=2155.96&end=2167.5' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How interesting are the maps of bombardment according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very boring",
            optionRight: "the most interesting things in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=52596f7e-9abb-11e6-b85a-089e01ba0770&start=2829.12&end=2852.59' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How boring has Gayle become according to herself?",
            optionLeft: "as boring as one could become",
            optionRight: "she is the most interesting person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=8375bfb2-8a86-11e6-b3a1-089e01ba034d&start=1462.09&end=1485.32' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How boring has the Guest become according to herself?",
            optionLeft: "as boring as one could become",
            optionRight: "she is the most interesting person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=0a4db1e0-6a2d-11e6-a28a-089e01ba034d&start=3110.58&end=3128.91' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How boring are `her` protesters according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most boring people in the world",
            optionRight: "the most interesting and active people in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=55b8be18-54ed-11e6-855f-089e01ba0335&start=2461.93&end=2473.89' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How boring was her date according to Woman 1?",
            optionLeft: "the most boring person in the world",
            optionRight: "the most interesting person in the world"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=cac3c3ea-1d22-11e6-b216-089e01ba0326&start=4530.85&end=4544.62' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How boring is her morning according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "there is nothing more boring than her mornings",
            optionRight: "her mornings are the most interesting mornings one can have"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=fa3f37f8-c4cb-11e5-800a-089e01ba0335&start=564.49&end=575.38' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How boring are the details in which Clinton explains her plans according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "the most tiring possible",
            optionRight: "very interesting"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=b5fd5666-ab65-11e6-bc38-089e01ba0770&start=110.82&end=120.88' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How big is Bill Hall Jr.`s secret according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "very unimportant trifle",
            optionRight: "the secret will forever change the lives of many in a negative way if it blows up"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=ba7f4198-b91d-11e6-aacf-2c600c9500f4&start=407.53&end=415.3' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How big are the waves according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "barely noticeable",
            optionRight: "tidal waves"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=c486da34-aba8-11e6-8597-089e01ba0326&start=508.83&end=527.85' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How big are the Centers of Disease Control and prevention according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as big as a local pharmacy",
            optionRight: "has big as Walmart (largest company in the world)"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=f2d807ce-a18e-11e6-8988-089e01ba0770&start=584.16&end=599.96' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How important is capital inflow to trade according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "negligible and only a small part, if any",
            optionRight: "most important and biggest part"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=4eca3502-cd0e-11e6-bac3-089e01ba0335&start=5282.92&end=5295.33' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How big is the backup according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "tiny, it is hardly a backup at all",
            optionRight: "the largest backup the world has ever seen"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=f5a320f8-ad21-11e6-b422-089e01ba0326&start=3228.57&end=3237.19' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How large is the extreme fraction of Islam in the religion according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "negligible, almost none",
            optionRight: "almost all people of Islam belong to the extreme fraction"         
	},
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=dc086c5a-a585-11e6-a674-089e01ba0326&start=2651.72&end=2669.58' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How small is his mother according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "as small as a 3 year old",
            optionRight: "as tall as an NBA player"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=16dbe2e4-a4be-11e6-9a66-089e01ba0335&start=1273.87&end=1285.03' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How small is the sweet according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "tiny, as small as a grain of rice",
            optionRight: "very large, about the size of a wedding cake"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=22d6cbb4-ce6b-11e6-af30-089e01ba0326&start=2423.11&end=2438.26' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How small is the boat according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small, one person can barely sit in it",
            optionRight: "the size of a cruise ship"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=ae6f90b2-c2f8-11e6-a1c7-089e01ba0338&start=2360.2&end=2372.97' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How small is the area according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small that nobody can move",
            optionRight: "open area, where everyone has their own property and land"
         },
	{
	    QUD: "Video", 
	    stimulus:"<video controls autoplay height='300' width='400' playcount='2' name='media' src='http://pisa.vrnewsscape.ucla.edu/newsscape_mp4_snippet.cgi?file=56d54f8e-b57b-11e6-ad52-089e01ba0770&start=5779.63&end=5793.0' type='video/mp4'>/video",
            question: "How wide are the streets in Florence according to the speaker?",
            optionLeft: "so small, a car barely fit",
            optionRight: "so side, 3 Trucks can easily fit"
         }
     ]
}

